funrelaxsite.com 2008-12-11

# Privacy Policy - Game Bear

Privacy 

funrelaxsite.com takes the privacy of its users seriously. We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our users while using our services. This Privacy Policy statement explains the data processing practices of funrelaxsite.com 

#### Personal data 

Through our Web site, gameingnow.com will not collect any personal data about you (e.g. your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address), unless you voluntarily choose to provide us with it (e.g. by registration, survey), respectively, provide your consent, or unless otherwise permitted by applicable laws and regulations for the protection of your personal data. 

#### Non-Personal Data Collected Automatically 

When you access our Web site, we may automatically (i.e., not by registration) collect non-personal data (e.g. type of Internet browser and operating system used, domain name of the Web site from which you came, number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed). We may use this data and to monitor the attractiveness of our Web site and improve its performance or content. 

#### Use of cookies 

Each time our website is visited, we use cookies to record the date and time of access to the site and any information read or downloaded. The details recorded by the cookies are not information which identifies the user and therefore is not personal information. A cookie is a small text file placed on your computer hard drive by a web page server, which can then be accessed by our web servers. You may configure your web browser not to accept cookies; however this may mean that you are not able to make full use of our website. 

#### Links to other websites 

funrelaxsite.com also provides links to affiliated sites. The privacy policies of these linked sites are the responsibility of the linked site and gameingnow.com has no control or influence over their policies. Please check the policies of each site you visit for specific information. funrelaxsite.com cannot be held liable for damage or misdoings of other sites linked or otherwise. 

funrelaxsite.com makes reasonable efforts to include accurate and up-to-date information on this Web site; it does not, however, make any representations as to its accuracy or completeness. Your use of this Web site is at your own risk. funrelaxsite.com, its authors, and the other parties involved in creating and delivering the contents of this Web site, are not liable for any damages arising from the use of this site. 

#### Questions and Feedback 

If you believe that the privacy of your personal information has been compromised or is not being adequately protected, you should contact us by emailing us at admin@funrelaxsite.com

#### Changes to this Privacy Statement 

This statement sets out our current Privacy Statement however we reserve the right to make changes from time to time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we shall post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
